Guide to the James McNamara Papers WAG.129
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series II: Mason Tenders Local of the Laborers International Union of North America (LIUNA), 1985-1996.
  - USA v. Mason Tenders: Declaration: Taffet, Allan N., Exhibit 131-132, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - USA v. Mason Tenders: Declaration: Taffet, Allan N., Exhibit 133-140, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - USA v. Mason Tenders: Declaration: Taffet, Allan N., Exhibit 141-150, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - USA v. Mason Tenders: Federal Supplement, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - USA v. Mason Tenders: Government Memo of Law In Support Of Motion, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - USA v. Mason Tenders: Notice Of Motion Against (I), 1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - USA v. Mason Tenders: Notice Of Motion Against (II), 1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - USA v. Mason Tenders: Order of Settlement, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - USA v. Mason Tenders: Press Releases, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - United States of America v. Messera, James et al.: Outline of Indictments, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Series III: International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, District Council 9, 1967-1995.
  - Benson, Herman: “Insurgency and Reform in the Painters, 1960-1987” (manuscript), undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Clippings and Press, 1967-1995 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1972-1991 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Drywall Tapers v. Operative Plasterers and Cement Masons, Local 530, 1974, 1982, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Election Materials, 1988-1995 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Government Memos on Corruption in District Council 9, 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Government Surveillance, undated, 1984-1987 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Government Surveillance: Affidavits in Support of Continuation, undated, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Government Surveillance: Progress Reports, undated, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Government Surveillance: Wire Tap Transcripts, undated, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Legal Briefs and Indictments: California Painters, 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Legal Briefs and Indictments: District Council 9, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - New York State v. Moscatiello, Lou (I), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - New York State v. Moscatiello, Lou (II), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Racketeering, 1990, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Union Publications, 1978, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Series IV: United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipefitting Industry, Plumbers Local #2 (Manhattan), 1964-1997.
  - Clippings and Press, 1964, 1967, 1992-1996 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Constitutions, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Department of Labor: Annual Reports, 1994-1997 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Department of Labor: Trusteeship Reports, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Election Materials, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Government Surveillance: Progress Report (I), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Government Surveillance: Progress Report (II), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Hearing of Local 2, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Legal Briefs and Indictments, 1988-1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Legal Briefs and Indictments, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Legal Briefs and Indictments, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Licensing: Public Advocate Report, “Enforcement Down The Drain”, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Series V: Service Employees International Union, Local 32 B-J, 1954-1999.
  - Agreements, 1990, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Annual Reports, 1991-1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Benefits, 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1991-1999 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1997 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Election By-Laws, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Election Materials, 1992-1997 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Flyers and Leaflets, 1954, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Job Training, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Legal Documents, 1990-1997 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - McGorman, James: Trial, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Press Releases, 1988-1996 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Rank and File Literature, 1990-1997 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Reports, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Strikes, 1993, 1996, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Series VI: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1968-1998.
  - Clippings, undated, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Clippings, 1995-1998 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Conferences: Strategic Plan, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1998 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Hoffa, James: Elections and Election Officer Decision re:, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Independent Review Board: Investigation of Ron Carey, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Independent Review Board: Request for Trusteeship Consideration, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Investigations Officer v. Salerno, Charles et al., 1990 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Rank and File Publications, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - United States v. Feinstein, Yvette et al., 1968, 1981, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - United States v. IBT, “La Cosa Nostra” et al., 1992 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Series VII: Building Trades Employers’ Association of the City of New York, 1945-1997.
  - Jurisdictional Disputes: Correspondence, 1945, 1978-1979, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Jurisdictional Disputes: Plans, 1976, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Series VIII: Unprocessed Material, 1990s-2000s.
  - Unprocessed Material, 1990s-2000s (Box 6)
  - Unprocessed Material, 1990s-2000s (Box 7)
  - Unprocessed Material, 1990s-2000s (Box 8)
  - Unprocessed Material, 1990s-2000s (Box 9)
  - Unprocessed Material, 1990s-2000s (Box 10)
  - Unprocessed Material, circa 1979-2000s (Box 11)